<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kmouth</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kmouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKMouthxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">K 语音精灵</name>
  <summary>Speech Synthesizer Frontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Frontal del sintetitzador de veu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Frontal del sintetitzador de veu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Oberfläche für Sprachsynthesizer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Speech Synthesiser Frontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Interfaz de síntesis de voz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Interface de sintetizador de voz.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Spraaksynthesizerfrontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Grensesnitt for talesyntese</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Interface de Síntese de Fala</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Rozhranie pre syntezátor reči</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Gränssnitt för talsyntes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Оболонка для синтезу мовлення з тексту</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSpeech Synthesizer Frontendxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">语音合成器前端</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
     KMouth is a program which enables persons that cannot speak to let their computer speak, e.g. mute people or people who have lost their voice. It has a text input field and speaks the sentences that you enter. It also has support for user defined phrasebooks.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KMouth és un programa que habilita a les persones que no poden parlar a que ho faci el seu ordinador, p. ex. la gent muda o la gent que ha perdut la seva veu. Té un camp d'entrada de text i pronuncia les frases que s'introdueixen. També permet llibres de frases definits per l'usuari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KMouth ist ein Programm, mit dem stumme Benutzer ihren Computer für sich sprechen lassen können. Es gibt ein Texteingabefeld, dessen Inhalt vorgelesen wird. Außerdem können benutzerdefinierte Textpassagenbücher benutzt werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KMouth is a program which enables persons that cannot speak to let their computer speak, e.g. mute people or people who have lost their voice. It has a text input field and speaks the sentences that you enter. It also has support for user defined phrasebooks.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KMouth é un programa que permite ás persoas que non poden falar que fagan que o seu computador fale, como a xente muda ou a xente que perdeu a voz. Ten un campo de entrada de texto e pronuncia as frases que se escriben. Tamén permite libros de frases definidos polo usuario.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KMouth is een programma die personen die niet kunnen spreken om hun computer te laten spreken, bijv. mensen zonder stem of mensen die hun stem hebben verloren. Het heeft een tekst invoerveld en spreekt de zinnen uit die u invoert. Het ondersteunt ook gebruikergedefinieerde boeken met frasen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KMouth é um programa que permite às pessoas que não conseguem falar deixar que o computador deles fale, p.ex. pessoas mudas ou que tenham perdido a sua voz. Tem um campo de texto e fala as frases que lá introduzir. Também tem suporte para livros de frases definidas pelo utilizador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KMouth — програма, яка надає змогу тим, хто не може говорити, спілкуватися за допомогою комп'ютера. У ній передбачено поле для введення тексту, який вимовлятиме комп'ютер. Також можна створювати визначені користувачем набори заздалегідь приготованих фраз.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKMouth is a program which enables persons that cannot speak to let their computer speak, e.g. mute people or people who have lost their voice. It has a text input field and speaks the sentences that you enter. It also has support for user defined phrasebooks.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KMouth 是为那些不能说话的人发声的程序，比如聋哑人或失声的人。它有一个文本输入框，可以输入您键入的语句。它也支持用户定义的短语集。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kmouth</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kmouth</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/applications/utilities/kmouth/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/kmouth.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmouth</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kmouth.desktop</launchable>
</component>
