<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kmouth</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kmouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KMouth</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKMouthxx</name>
  <summary>Speech Synthesizer Frontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Frontal del sintetitzador de veu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Speech Synthesiser Frontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Spraaksynthesizerfrontend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Interface de Síntese de Fala</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Gränssnitt för talsyntes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Оболонка для синтезу мовлення з тексту</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSpeech Synthesizer Frontendxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
     KMouth is a program which enables persons that cannot speak to let their computer speak, e.g. mutal people or people who have lost their voice. It has a text input field and speaks the sentences that you enter. It also has support for user defined phrasebooks.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KMouth és un programa que habilita a les persones que no poden parlar a que ho faci el seu ordinador, p. ex. la gent muda o la gent que ha perdut la seva veu. Té un camp d'entrada de text i pronuncia les frases que s'introdueixen. També permet llibres de frases definits per l'usuari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KMouth is a program which enables persons that cannot speak to let their computer speak, e.g. mute people or people who have lost their voice. It has a text input field and speaks the sentences that you enter. It also has support for user defined phrase books.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KMouth is een programma die personen die niet kunnen spreken om hun computer te laten spreken, bijv. mensen zonder stem of mensen die hun stem hebben verloren. Het heeft een tekst invoerveld en spreekt de zinnen uit die u invoert. Het ondersteunt ook gebruikergedefinieerde boeken met frasen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KMouth é um programa que permite às pessoas que não conseguem falar deixar que o computador deles fale, p.ex. pessoas mudas ou que tenham perdido a sua voz. Tem um campo de texto e fala as frases que lá introduzir. Também tem suporte para livros de frases definidas pelo utilizador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kmouth är ett program som gör det möjligt för personer som inte kan tala att låta datorn tala, t.ex. stumma eller personer som har förlorat rösten. Det har ett textinmatningsfält och läser upp meningarna som skrivs in. Det har också stöd för användardefinierade parlörer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KMouth — програма, яка надає змогу тим, хто не може говорити, спілкуватися за допомогою комп'ютера. У ній передбачено поле для введення тексту, який вимовлятиме комп'ютер. Також можна створювати визначені користувачем набори заздалегідь приготованих фраз.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKMouth is a program which enables persons that cannot speak to let their computer speak, e.g. mutal people or people who have lost their voice. It has a text input field and speaks the sentences that you enter. It also has support for user defined phrasebooks.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kmouth</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kmouth</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/applications/utilities/kmouth/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/kmouth.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmouth</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kmouth.desktop</launchable>
</component>
